Doctor summary (to see all details, run flutter doctor -v):
[ÔêÜ] Flutter (Channel stable, 3.38.9, on Microsoft Windows [Versi┬ón 10.0.26200.7840], locale es-EC)
[ÔêÜ] Windows Version (11 Home Single Language 64-bit, 25H2, 2009)
[X] Android toolchain - develop for Android devices
    X Unable to locate Android SDK.
      Install Android Studio from: https://developer.android.com/studio/index.html
      On first launch it will assist you in installing the Android SDK components.
      (or visit https://flutter.dev/to/windows-android-setup for detailed instructions).
      If the Android SDK has been installed to a custom location, please use
      `flutter config --android-sdk` to update to that location.

[X] Chrome - develop for the web (Cannot find Chrome executable at .\Google\Chrome\Application\chrome.exe)
    ! Cannot find Chrome. Try setting CHROME_EXECUTABLE to a Chrome executable.
[X] Visual Studio - develop Windows apps
    X Visual Studio not installed; this is necessary to develop Windows apps.
      Download at https://visualstudio.microsoft.com/downloads/.
      Please install the "Desktop development with C++" workload, including all of its default components
[ÔêÜ] Connected device (2 available)
[ÔêÜ] Network resources

! Doctor found issues in 3 categories.
